legerweb.com 2018-08-12

# Privacy Policy

## Leger (Legerweb.com) Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers personally identifiable information that Legerweb.com collects when you are on the Legerweb.com site, and when you answer Legerweb.com Surveys. This policy also covers any personally identifiable information that Legerweb.com business partners share with Leger.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Leger does not own or control or to people that Leger does not employ or manage, including without limitation, any Leger affiliates or business partners.

## Information Collection and Use

Legerweb.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Legerweb.com account, when you are answering a Legerweb.com survey and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Legerweb.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners, and business clients.

When you register with Legerweb.com, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, postal code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Legerweb.com and sign up with our services, you are not anonymous to us, but when you answer a Survey, your profile and opinions are not directly associated to your name.

Legerweb.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Legerweb.com cookie information and the page you requested.

Legerweb.com uses information for the following general purposes: to create a specific sample in order to send you Surveys, and to pick our monthly draw winner.

Legerweb.com also makes use of Google Analytics features (Display Advertising, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Legerweb uses this data to identify member interests and improve our contests and promotional campaigns. Using the [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), users can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. You can also explore Google Analytics' currently available [opt-out options](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for the web.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Legerweb.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.  
Legerweb.com will not share personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people unless:

We have your consent to share this information;  
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;  
We need to share the information with companies who work on behalf of Leger to provide a product or service to you. Please know that whenever we share your personal information with these trusted business partners, they work under confidentiality agreements. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);  
We reasonably believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required or permitted by law;  
We respond to warrants, subpoenas, court orders or legal process or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or  
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Legerweb.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.  
We may transfer information about you if Legerweb.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Legerweb.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
When you register for a Legerweb.com account, your registration information and other data will be transmitted to the United States and/or other countries for processing and storage by Legerweb.com and its affiliates and may be subject to the legal jurisdiction of these countries.

## Cookies

Legerweb.com may set and access Legerweb.com cookies on your computer. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Legerweb.com cookies.  
You have the ability to edit and delete your account information and preferences.  
You have the right to access, verify and update your Legerweb.com account information and preferences at any time.

You may request deletion of your Legerweb.com account by visiting our Account Deletion page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Please click here to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

## Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees, who within the scope of their job need this information to provide products or services to you.  
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information.  
In the event that you believe your personal safety is at risk, or if you believe that you may be the victim of identity theft or other illegal conduct, please contact the appropriate federal, provincial or local law enforcement agencies directly.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Leger may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Legerweb.com account or by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

## Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, or wish to contact our Privacy Officer, please contact us by clicking here

Legerweb.com is owned and managed by:Leger  
507 Place d’Armes, Suite 700  
Montreal, Quebec, Canada  
H2Y 2W8  
1-800-404-2464  

To unsubscribe from the Legerweb.com panel and/or Leger newsletter  
Please use one of the following email addresses:  
* Email us to unsubscribe@legerweb.com  
* Visit us at <https://legerweb.com/unsubscribe>  
* Call us at 1-800-404-2464  
* Mail us at legerweb.com, 700-507 Place d’Armes, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, H2Y 2W8

Last updated May 15, 2012
